Prophet T.B. Joshua At Paul And Silas' Prison in Philippi, Greece
The Lord said we should use here as a point of contact to pray for you and pray for the nations.
Anywhere you are right now, be with me by faith and receive.
By the covenant Word in my heart, I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Just as Paul and Silas were released, be released, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever situation you are in, be it sickness, hardship, poverty, affliction,
isolation, rejection, depression, just name them -
By the covenant Word in my heart, I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Here – a spiritual monument.
What you have read in the Bible about Paul and Silas, how they were imprisoned -
this is not just historic; it is real. Indeed, a place of the Bible, the land of the Bible.
Here we are.
Paul and Silas were released by the Word in their heart.
The Word in their heart became the key that opened the prison gate.
Be Thou in my heart – release you, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever way you might have been connected to satan, to demons by way of poverty,
sickness, disease, isolation, depression, unbelief – I disconnect you, in the name of Jesus!
Be set free!
I speak to the nations all over the world.
Troubled nations, in whatever area you are troubled, at war against one another, disunity,
hatred around the world, whatever way you, troubled nations,
trouble – I command you cease, in the name of Jesus!
I send a Word to my nation, you trouble, cease, in the name of Jesus!
I loose you, in the name of Jesus, from all troubles you are facing.
I say to you, you trouble, be thou loosed!
I release you from sickness and diseases, affliction – whatever!
The Bible said Paul and Silas prayed to God to comfort and support them in their trial.
Be comforted, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever area of your life, be comforted, in the name of Jesus!
Receive strength to go on and on.
Receive strength!
In your nation, receive strength!
I pray for you all that are with me in Spirit.
This is Paul and Silas’ prison.
It is in the Bible, if I may read in the Acts of the Apostles.
Acts 16:25 - ”About midnight, Paul and Silas were praying and singing hymns to God,
and the other prisoners were listening to them.
Suddenly, there was such a violent earthquake that the foundations of the prison were shaken.
At once, all the prison doors flew open, and everyone’s chains came loose.”
Right now, chain of poverty, isolation, sickness, disease -
everyone’s chains right now, come loose, in the name of Jesus!
I release you from every chain.
Chain of poverty, isolation, whatever way he might have connected you to himself,
come loose, in the name of Jesus!
I break the chain, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear the chain loosing.
I can hear the noise of the chain loosing.
Be loosed, in the name of Jesus! Be free, in the name of Jesus!
By covenant Word, I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Oh my God.
It’s as if I should not leave here because I can feel the presence of God.
I feel the presence of God more than ever before.
I want you to feel what I am feeling; the presence of God is all over!
The atmosphere is quite awesome.
There is so much trouble in the world: Family trouble, nation trouble, community trouble.
These are synonymous to satan.
Satan uses those things to connect people to himself.
I break that connection.
The word it uses here is clear.
Acts 16:26 – “At once, all the prison doors flew open and everyone’s chains came loose.”
Whatever way satan might have connected you, whatever way satan might have dealt with you,
whatever way satan must have related with you, like I said, he is synonymous to trouble,
sickness, disease, affliction, isolation, barrenness – just name whatever -
all these troubles all over the world – satan is synonymous to them.
He is the architect; he is the manufacturer.
He produces them.
Satan and trouble.
Satan and affliction.
Satan and violence.
Satan and disease.
Satan and affliction, just name them – I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Just like everyone here in the Bible.
Like it is written here, in Paul and Silas’ prison.
Acts 16:26 – “At once, all the prison doors flew open and everyone’s chains came loose.”
Everyone’s chain, under the influence of my voice, come loose, in the name of Jesus!
Be disconnected!
I disconnect you from satan and all his evil, sickness and diseases, attacks, trials, affliction.
I disconnect you right now from all these, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Acts 16:27 – “The jailer woke up, and when he saw the prison doors open, he draw his sword
and was about to kill himself because he thought the prisoners had escaped.”
It is just a place we are talking about.
Viewers – I want to leave you.
Everyone under the influence of my voice, wherever you are, whatever you are doing,
see – I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Come loose, you chain! Come loose, in the name of Jesus!
Loose, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever way satan might have connected you, be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
He is synonymous to trouble, sickness, disease and affliction.
Become loose! I loose you, in the name of Jesus!
I separate you, right now!
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Thank you, Jesus!
Thank you once again.
I want to ask you, have you made to Heaven?
It is not too late.
You just have to surrender; give your life to Jesus!
Say, Lord Jesus, come into my heart today. Wash me with Your precious blood.
Save my soul.
You are the only One that can save my soul.
You are my Redeemer, Healer, Deliverer.
Thank You Lord, in Jesus Christ name. Amen.
Thank You Lord.